automobile.com 2004-12-04

# Buy a car. Buy a car made easy. Buy a new car

| 

**Buy a car** with confidence. Buying a new car with a new car quote puts you in a strong position when buying your **new car** from trusted dealers. With a **free new car quote** , dealers commit to a new car price, though you are under no obligation to buy a new car. Choose any new car and within 48 hours you will receive your free new car quote. Preparing yourself to **buy a new car** has never been easier. We connect you with the products and services you need to buy a new car. 

|    

#### Automobile Inc. Privacy Policy

Automobile Inc. connects people with automobile products and services. In order to provide our users with various services, including free car quotes, we need to gather and supply personal information about prospective car buyers. We will not abuse your personal information and will use it only as outlined below. 

#### How does Automobile Inc. operate?

Automobile Inc. ("we") operate a variety of services, the main one being a system which introduces new car shoppers to new car retailers or retail networks. 

"Automobile.com" is owned, controlled, and operated in its entirety by us.

The buying service itself (hereafter referred to as "the Process" or "we") is controlled and operated by us. This Privacy Policy covers the gathering and use of information identifiable to you which is performed by the Process. 

#### Information Collected Automatically by Our Web Servers 

We use your IP address, collected automatically by our Web servers, to analyze our traffic sources and to discourage fraudulent use of the Process. This information does not identify you personally. 

The Process places "cookies" on your hard drive. Cookies are small amounts of textual information which allow the Process to work better for you by storing information such as the vehicle you're currently configuring, etc. These cookies are only used by the Process during the time you're in the Process. We don't collect them or use them in other ways. You can set your browser preferences so that you don't accept cookies, or only accept them on demand. 

#### Information Collected Through Our Online Forms 

If you have been matched by the Process software to a retail channel for which we gather the personal information, we need you to voluntarily provide your name, email address, phone number, and other information to make the introduction possible. We will provide it to the retailer or retail network to whom we're introducing you. The retailer or retail network will then use the information to contact you regarding your request. 

#### General Information 

We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of external partners. 

If we are required by law through court order or subpoena to release personal information, we will comply. This has never occurred in the history of our company and we consider the possibility of this occurring in the future to be remote. 

We reserve the right to change or amend this Privacy Policy at any time in response to changing business needs. Please check regularly for updates which may affect your use of Automobile Inc. services.

|   
---|---|---
